We will do itu./Benar
To 9 kali./8
I mean this time I promise
Hold tolong./Benarkah./Maaf
Start baru./Benar
New Start 9./Hei number I could still
cancel their internet
I think you're not doing enough
Are you okay?
What is happening?
Um...
Yes, ah
No
Now we must also call an electrician
You try not to stay up
The first day of school and everything,
okay
Hey, are you hungry? / I'm fine
See you tonight
Oh god, do not die, do not die , honey,
are you OK?
Are you hurt? Are you hurt? Are you
hurt?
Are you all right? / Yeah, I'm okay
I do this every day
Um...
We are no games
I'll be back
Do you want to discover the secrets of
the universe
Think of energy, frequency
And vibration, nicola tesla
Okay, start
And start
And we have a new student here
Mcgrath./Max Mr. McGrath
Here
You are not a child of Jim McGrath,
right? / Yeah, something like that
Ya./Dia outstanding people
Where I sat
This semester we will dive into the
power of our thoughts
Hey
Are you OK? / Yes, I ..
Thank
Back backward
It keren./Terimakasih truck
I dapatkan./Benarkah
Do not look shocked
What do I know I'm no bike
You named him, right
Okay
As new
No power
Oh, it's strange
I .. I tried to ..
Be careful ..
McGrath
Hai./Hei./Oh God, look at you
You remember Miles, right?
Yes, yes
I tahu./Aku people
Randomly send you a Christmas gift
Yes benar./Tentu Do you remember
You work with ayahku./Benar
Miles will join us when dinner, so
you'd better shower
Come
It was 4 0./Baik
Come on. You ready?
We are no power outages
25 mile radius
Impossible
How? / 25 mi radius./Itu Cool
The police do not think so
But your father always smooth operator,
he denied
He's very special, dad
It bersinar./Itu not shine in 15 years
So you arrive arrived in touch?
The first time we met
Actually Miles convince me to come
Really? Okay, why here Brendan./Ini
fault
What is it
Come
The first day sekolah./Benarkah? /Ya
How? / Ah
Okay, more crowded than usual
Come on, come
Come on, come on, come
Fixed prone
Quick
Please stop playing with your chair,
you will ruin it
Okay, close pintunya./Segelnya
I get him
It's too banyak./Jadi why do you do it
I'll see your file, your father is a
true visionary, not me
Miles rebuild Ntech, he is running now
I prefer when there husband
Everything we do today is based on the
vision of father
Your father wants to save the world, and
We just follow the prompts
We almost made a breakthrough
What happened?
Forget ../ No what, do not worry
What?
Miles night there when the accident
He's trying to save your father
Make sure you're not dead
No,
He was not a child lagi./Ya, he was a
small child
Now we are here not to play spams./Oh
thank god
We like spams, do not ever expire
So what I miss? / Desserts
Can I get you something from the
kitchen?
You want to come in the office to see
what your father created
The door is always open
Terimakasih./Aku must say, you remind
me of your father
Although higher banyak./Jauh more
You were spirits. It is calculated
Welcome malam./Bye
Listen
I'll sleep
Yes bob, tonight is the big question
What makes the tornado come to this area
Security camera footage shows
Come on.
Come on...
What?
What the hell
Max, you plug something?
Good
Okay
Nyala
What?
I can not hear what you say
What? / He says typing mess
I'll find
Hai./Hei
You go out tonight
Finding something nice? / I did not
find any bad
Hey, I'm the cute today
It was the most embarrassing in the
whole house
Wow, thanks, it's an honor
I
It's heading in the basement bomb
shelter
Father always bersiap./Untuk what?
Zombie Apocalypse?
I heard you talk with Miles
Why is everyone in this city more than
I know my father
What do you mean? I'm talking about
your father along waktu./Tidak, you do
not
I do not know anything about his past ,
because you do not talk about it
I do not know her job, her family or
How does he die
Listen
I want you to know your father
I see a lot in you, he's a very unusual
But he is so complicated story
And I just do not know if you
If I'm what? / Ready
Ah, sorry
Hei./Kau menemukannya./Ya, I'm late
Not apa./Apa this?
What? / Try it
Oh, the texture is a little strange
Thank
No problem
Frida
What? / My name is Frida
Rita, wow./Ya, saja./Ya it to your
information, you do not have to worry
Your secret is safe with me.
As you know, I also know secret. I know
you're trying to hide.
What?
You do not associate with anyone
You do not attract much attention
But you talk, so I think you're weird
You're good enough to be alone
Without so reclusive
It is, put your number in my calls,
I'll take you around the at anytime
Give you tur./Ya. Hei./Kau better
I think your call
What ..
Actually, I had to the bathroom
No
Max./Aku have to go
Sorry
Max
What?
Max, time to get up
Max
Capital
Max./Tidak, backward, away from me, I
commemorated, retreat
No, stop, I say backward
OK, OK
No, you say my name, what did you say?
Max, max./Kau okay up there?
What do you want? / Decrease max weapon
Oh god, do you speak English
You're what? Some sort of robot? / I is
parasitic life forms based on silicon,
my name .. ah, wait
Something rhymes with .. I get this
Wait, Axel
Stell, he called Steel./Siapa?
I do not know, but one thing
I menemukanmu./Kau darimana./Ah, good
question
I'm from ..
From a different world ../ Yes, I guess
Namamu./Ya, and you is Max McGrath
Ya./Aku here trying to protect you from
all those who try to kill us
You have a crazy amount of energy ,
which
With a thermometer, clock, dear to not
waste
Wait, Max Steel
What is this? / What do you know about
energy?
What is this?
Steel./Ya./Max what are you doing up
there
Oh god, my mom comes, you have to hide
What is she dangerous?
Oh no
How tua./Kau have to clean
Max./Ada what?
Are you okay? / Yes, I'm fine fine, I
just ..
I'm a nightmare, fell out of bed
I called last night
You sleep when I got home, are you okay?
/ I'm fine
Course
Uh, no, I just exercise
I want to take laundrymu./Tidak, I
could do laundryku alone now
Strange sometimes, and you'll be late
There was an explosion and
I can, I can
What are you doing, watch me
Why did you do it? / There is energy in
you
I menyerapnya./Max./Sama same
I'll leave
Not Max, hear
You will produce energy takion all your
life, and that's what I eat
Without it I actually starve to death
Once you
Once you know what? / Yes
We are together forever
Well, I want to know all that you know
sekarang./Oke
Okay, how energy
Takion it, where they come from
Uh .. the past
You're doing this to me? / No, I guess
you do this to me
You wake aku./Kau going to kill me? /
Yes
Actually, you do not realize how lucky
you are to me there
Yesterday to melegakanmu of energy
berlebihanmu
Because you just will meledak./Baik, I
understand
So what, you're like a vampire space?
{AD]
Excuse Max, why do we hide
You're an alien? They membedahmu or
what?
Dissecting is open organisms die to be
learned
That makes no sense, because I do not
die
Great work Max, now
See This
We are connected with Max
It's okay, I did not see it
Spread, found
They chase us
Who wants to kill you? / Who wants to
kill us
Ayolah./Aku not know
I've told everything I ingat./Tunggu ,
wait
Wait, I remember something else
Do not do
What is it?
What the hell is it? / I do not know, I
saw him too
I like building
As I recall, but I see you
I see refleksimu, I was you
It's your memory, why do I see your
memory
I told you, we're connected
You did not hear aku./Aku hear about ..
Ultralink./Apa it you? / Ulterlink.
No, it's very dangerous , they
They destroy the world, they destroy
everything
They come, we should go from here
They come kebumi./Karena ibuku./Tidak
you're afraid, because people with a
gun chasing us
Because you think we are attacked
We had to go to a certain place where
they will not attack us
I can not believe I'm doing this
Hei./Hai
You can not do it, you want them
dissect ?
That I remember
You have to calm, understand mengerti.
/Aku
I do not control suhuku
Measure the area of point A to point B
Mutual this formula, because this will
be in the final
This being lied
Do not trust
I let ipodku flame
What did you do, do not lie
Are you crazy? / We're in attack
We're under attack
You save aku./Selamatkan I
It was heavy
Basic stupid, I hate
Fear
See Max, I protect you
It aku./Sofia
What happened to you yesterday
Are you okay? / Yes
Yes, I'm sorry
Merusaknya./Bukan I feel that, right
No, I'm just a person who is too weird
Maybe I can make it up to you
Yes, and how are you doing itu./Oke
Are you sure ../ Yes
We can talk about this later
I had to run, will be late for
Zumbaku class
Creature that girl makes heart rate and
breathing increases
Perhaps you should avoid dealing with
dia./Mungkin you must be silent
See, he's upset
Okay, we should go from here
I do not know Max
Creature was definitely put you mind
control virus
We might have to kill dia./Apa? No
Her name is Sofia, by the way, he
He ../ Cyborg
She was a woman, conch
Alien. No, I'm not dangerous alien./Dia
Okay
I can not
Maybe she can help us
I could not tell him, all my life him
crazy with my health
With all the doctors he encounters
Not what
I will not hentikan./Kalau upset you,
you generate energy
Clearly upset my mum
No, he just...
It payah./Apa?
All that happened he moved from place
to place
Yes, I understand
What is it? / Why do I tell you this ?
/ Because I'm here for you, max
I'm here to protect you, it means you
can tell me everything
Max
Sometimes I wish my dad was here
It deals
You know this sounds
I do not know, I miss him
I understand
I know you know where my house
I listened
Good
Sorry
Yes, it's okay, I'm fine
I can help you remember who wants
membunuhmu./Kita
Well, if you remember something I do
not know
Perhaps more than memory we have seen,
could help us
Um, this
Max. view
What? This?
You remember Ntek./Mereka attacking us
They will come to kita./Orang the black
clothes? / Not
Ultrans, they always come
Ayo./aku just ..
Believe itu./Serius./Semua max
Max, wait
Okay
Okay, so if you do not remember the
details, how we practice what we have
There is remind you of something? /Ya.
/Apa?
No, you go, I go, I guess you have to
create something
Oh, do not ..
You can stop./Aku will continue to do
this
How do you do it? / I do not, we do,
I'm telling you, if we work together,
we can harmonisasikan takion energy
Order to become energy turbo./Turbo?
True? / Yes, yes, it's very powerful
Energy can improve the attributes
fisikmu./Seperti what? / Try
Yes, it's funny
Wow, did you see that?
It was biasa./Lumayan
It was incredible, but Max, you know
what is more interesting?
My knowledge about energy, I no volume
Not mungkin./Oke
We'll take care of this
Problems
Okay, we can go back if you mau./Ya
The Start
Ya./Apa okay?
Why do not you like this
It's not your man
But next
You give
They know about this?
Oh yes, it tastes good
Harmonization, this is for you
Still bertahan./Keren
We are within striking distance
It was my father
You know my father
I tahu./Bagaimana you know my father
I do not
I was when your father died tornado
It's not the usual tornado Max
Steel
Yes, just look at what there is remind
me of any
Good Datang./Kita
What do you want didapur
You contact Molly McGrath, leave a
message
What do we do?
Let there
And somehow there are monsters
Actually, it was super scary
It was not an accident, it tornado
creation
That sort of storm
What? I do not ..
Sofia./Max./Oke, I want you to pause,
please
You want me to hit you / No, I want you
to run away.
Did you just shut my mouth? / Danger / A
Max behind us.
Well I have to go, sorry.
It's not going terjaid.
Max we have two vans chasing.
Okay we need something like a plan.
Okay time to dress / No we should have
to...
What, you do not like the shirt? / I do
not know, we have to split up.
Okay if you tell them in the run chase.
Or something
I protect you Max.
Give me time / Quiet, how I war
strategy.
For Example... you do not care.
You know
Damn / All the units we are lame.
Hey / Sofia / I'm not finished with you.
Listen now not a good time.
I'm really good on you, you keep away
from me.
Now it so I just.
You must come with me / What?
I do not know what I where / Mana.
It Entach / That two-mile away.
Good let road / Max.
Please.
Login
Are you sure you do not anything at all?
Never better.
It's a long story.
What happened?
Uh...
Father I died here when I was very
young.
Anything in the back will be a big
problem but.
What is wrong?
I'm sorry.
There is nothing.
I give the name of the bike I was.
And you any suggestions? / Good.
You want frontage something more
friendly to children.
Children true friends?
Because the toy which you said.
You said
Wow.
Yes.
Okay you know what time we got out of
our bike ride.
It tunganan classic, you'll see.
The next time we go out.
Yes.
Max.
Max / I'm not sure you'll take my offer.
It Sofia
He Bandu I / O sofia howdy.
Official tour guide, let's go.
It's wonderful / No thanks.
We just got a job Max's father.
You know when I met Jim 20 years ago,
he had no energy.
It is inspiring
I feel lucky to have colleagues with
him even if too short.
Hey can I talk to you?
Sure / Mari.
Please sit down.
I want to ask questions.
Sit / No, I want wondering about my dad.
What happens when the night he died /
Max.
That's not where I / Please.,
AKu need to know.
When I was there Billy go and
Your father he is. The circumstances I
say this.
I show you something, look at this.
What is this? / That prototype
miniature of core labor
Can anyone take energy people who want
to try.
It's your father's dream.
So what happened? / Your father was
good friends
Too genius, but sometimes he wants
To jump before you look.
And the energy that he planned / Wait ..
I do not understand what's wrong she? /
No, I say sometimes.
no intention to reach farther than we
wanted to.
Hey you're not anything at all?
I have to go / Max.
He was the habit of doing it.
Must bilangin him.
Father.
Ah... / Max.
Get out of here.
You should go from here I do not stop
the car.
Samasama.
Survive max.
See I told you to stay together / AKu
can not.
I can not see / Oh well wait a minute.
Love is something / You take one.
AKu like this / Where it go?
That's it from the memory of ultra link.
What we do / Max of face no known
enemies.
Shame it was shut off / What are you
talking about? / You see max.
It's war strategy we are not there a
lot.
Time to go, time go now.
Faster, run faster.
What happens in the armor?
He outboard for harmonization us / Why?
Have to work with Max.
Get down.
Do you miss / Thanks to that point.
Hold... / Help.
Stell.
Max look up there appears, shoot it.
Come turbo / What? / Quick before
lenawan wind.
Concentration and shoot.
We need contact cleaner / Oh really
Love it.
What is it? / Uh
Not clear.
It's you, why is it you?
No ultra-resistant Steel link / Good.
What are you doing, you fox power core.
Please.
I believe you / No.
You're one of them, you're ultra link /
No, I mean.
I think I did, but I do not like them.
I can not believe you / max ultra link
here to destroy the earth.
And the energy you are the only who can
stop it / Yes you there is energy well,
you kill for it.
No Max I remember I fought on the side
of your father.
We use this energy to ultra opponent
link, you and I do the same.
I can not do this,
I can not win against monsters and talk
to the aliens / Yes you can.
Your father / dad I die, you understand
that?
I do not have anyone, I alone / max no
you did not.
Max / Stay away from me / No, I said
get away from me.
Come on.
Come on...
Sofia.
Are you crazy? reduce your voice.
My God, what happened, you got an
accident / Yes.
Let me among you to the hospital.
I did not come into / I do not have
time / You're acting strange.
I'll tell you everything I promise.
Now people who I love in trouble,
because I am.
How can I do? / I need a phone.
Your Truck, and a pair of gloves .
Quick / I need your help, I do not know
Pelanpelan, who was your mother / I do
not know.
AKu not know iini people menejar me, and
What tejradi? / How tonight.
You're in plih it does.
Wait you know about it / Max heard me
biakbaik.
People
Grab your mother, do not want him, they
want you.
It's a trap / I do not know where he is?
You were the remaining
Listen to me baikbaik the session.
No... come on.
Mother.
Max where you / O mistress regret.
Yes / It Sofia I friend
From Max what he return? / No.
He did not, of Sofia.
Do you know where he is? / He came to
meet me.
And bring phone me and my car.
He was acting strangely, encountered
physician Edward and ran.
Mrs what things are not anything at
all.
Yes uh.
Everything good
I call you back.
Miles Edward told you to kill Steel.
Yes ma'am.
I'm still a big stake holders in Mtech
So the person you're taking orders I,
do you understand?
Yes bu / Good.
Now go find my son.
Steel.
It scrambles parts / How many.
Dozens maybe if we're lucky / We no
time there was a storm
Ultra link what would you be like her?
/ No.
You do not like iron.
First endanger the lives
This menambil / I'm not ready for this
/ Yes.
We did, how long.
The engine usability.
Can stop them together.
There is a strong wind
Steel resistant ultra link.
I turn on the point.
90 miles per hour.
When all firing operation.
We fled with steel we should siapsiap
in twenty seconds.
That touchdown / Large.
Trying.
You ready? / You.
Always.
Let's finish this.
That man cap / Includes the outside
world.
When space kit stuck there's not much
time.
I guess it was not too fast.
There's something wrong, auto defense
has at sabotage.
Awas.
Behind you
You working for merka.
You do what / steeel.
Max please / Call rebel you rebel you
know it.
Listen to me.
No / We are too old colleague Jim.
I asked you / Why are you doing this?
You do not know what they are.
Merka in manamenang / I make an
agreement.
I destroy you and ultra link.
I believe you / not you believe him.
You were received suggestions.
Turn on the power / And I'll kill you.
I will drain you.
From your energy there.
No....
Damn.
Sialan./Aku can remove you, you're
wrong, hear.
I can hear you.
I can take care of fellow bank / No.
You'll stay in a blast you're safe in
the world.
Let's do two no tax revenue.
Find him / Dad.
Go protect.
He was the only yuang important.
You made this very easy.
You know what I used to be, I'm not
sure you can grasp energy,
So let me know monseter coming.
Your father's QUESTIONS assure you.
Semuanyya?
Thank you / For I waited.
The entire time I spent I work with
this head.
There is the energy that we
acceleration.
Do this / This appliance energy.
Link ultra link, you came here / I
hiduphidup kill you.
Life. you source me.
Energy, now stepping there look like.
And your father left / should.
Hey
Your father alien max.
Alienx.
Do not be so dramatic, you think you're
a hero like your father.
You are not anything at all like him,
you alone and can not win.
You're alone, now stepping into it.
Walked there / Good.
I'm sorry Steel.
I'm sorry I doubted you / you name
Macrak father.
He's my friend, we choose to protect
the earth.
Together.
What are you doing.
Come energy.
I still want energy / Hey.
You're wrong I'm not alone
Not possible.
Steel now.
We trust you, we trust you .
You make mistakes / You want power.
Come come get me.
It completes Max / Come max wake.
Let's see you can not it's good sangkap
Max we should avoid it claw, grab
energy that you
I think it's a thought, what we do.
We're trying.
You think united with the monster fox
will you be a hero.
You're not a hero.
Stay away dair children.
Everything came out.
He's too strong.
What we lkaukan.
Max I remember.
Hello Max.
You send esuatuSesuatu / It was like
his father.
What she became.
So whatever he wants.
We do not run away
Back / yes.
We need a plan, war strategy
People haubs was sinking.
Come Max / What is.
That he / What is.
We give what he wants / What?
Actually this is stressful.
There's no one here to save you let .
Steel he police get it?
I do not know
This is my son, sekarnag.
You can be smart or you could be dead,
I choose clever father you choose
differently
How about you max?
As I told the father I dtang
You're just like your father.
You want strength you take it.
Steel now turbo / Good Max.
You give everything I needed / Yes sir.
Kareena I no energy is too much, I'll
explode.
It's for my dad.
Hey.
World.
Hi
Hey Come on please.
Come on.
It should be an animal, I could not
lose come.
You see Max
We're no fun together.
Thank honor.
It seems strange / AKu rsa was drunk.
As Nesty.
Where / Right there.
Now what?
No, you.
Tidak./Ad wailayahnya / What we do.
It was very good / Max.
Be careful / Yes.
Yes good / Suggest you go back to the
canyon energy jagajaga have me.
I'm trying to help you.
But I killed for you.
So many years try to hide this from you.
Because I was afraid
But akserang I No child banggap me.
What's your name? / Sorry
Do you think I want stars and magic.
Why did not they come to me?
I do not know maybe you do not no power
you have.
But you're in danger now will come at
you.
AKu think I can protect me wherever I
am.
Ya make me feel like it.
I know one thing okay.
You will not have to do this alone.
I love you my friend / I love you
Oh hey.
That's too long.
Yes for you.
I do not understand.
You will understand.
Show me.
Need to know you from where she guilty,
to know what he is.
Thank you father.
Hey / You do not have anything at all /
Yes.
You're from anywhere.
Uh I was crazy story / Try.
Listen uh.
I just stop by and tell you.
I used alone
Good enough on it.
I guess this time it was.
And then you have to.
Thank you to tell me.
What ini./Buka.
We have a lot of that talk.
Yes uh
Well I say that in talking about.
Tonight / Yes
Yes Nice
I see you later Max.
Okay
Ow wow / Okay, maybe you're onto him
Yes you think.
Flying Mode
Clothes no bias / Surely we fly you
complain about clothes.
Go to the right / To the left / You
know what straight.
OK.